<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tasty</string>
    <string name="asian_chicken_ind">1. ¼ cup sesame seeds\n2. 1 (16 ounce) package bow tie pasta\n3. ½ cup vegetable oil\n4. ⅓ cup light soy sauce\n5. ⅓ cup rice vinegar\n6. 1 teaspoon sesame oil
\n7. 3 tablespoons white sugar
\n8. ½ teaspoon ground ginger
\n9. ¼ teaspoon ground black pepper
\n10. 3 cups shredded, cooked chicken breast meat
\n11. ⅓ cup chopped fresh cilantro
\n12. ⅓ cup chopped green onion</string>
    <string name="asian_chicken_pro">  Heat a skillet over medium-high heat. Add sesame seeds, and cook stirring frequently until lightly toasted. Remove from heat, and set aside.

 \n\n
  Bring a large pot of lightly salted water to a boil. Add pasta, and cook for 8 to 10 minutes, or until al dente. Drain pasta, and rinse under cold water until cool. Transfer to a large bowl.

 \n\n
  In a jar with a tight-fitting lid, combine vegetable oil, soy sauce, vinegar, sesame oil, sugar, sesame seeds, ginger, and pepper. Shake well.

 \n\n
  Pour sesame dressing over pasta, and toss to coat evenly. Gently mix in chicken, cilantro, and green onions.</string>
    <string name="rice_pudding_ind">1. 3/4 cup uncooked white rice\n2. 2 cups milk, divided\n3. 1/3 cup white sugar\n5.1/4 teaspoon salt1 egg, beaten\n6. 2/3 cup golden raisins1 tablespoon butter\n7. 1/2 teaspoon vanilla extract</string>
    <string name="rice_pudding_pro">
        Bring 1 1/2 cups water to a boil in a saucepan; stir rice into boiling water. Reduce heat to low, cover, and simmer for 20 minutes.
\n\nIn a clean saucepan, combine 1 1/2 cups cooked rice, 1 1/2 cups milk, sugar and salt. Cook over medium heat until thick and creamy, 15 to 20 minutes. Stir in remaining 1/2 cup milk, beaten egg, and raisins; cook 2 minutes more, stirring constantly. Remove from heat and stir in butter and vanilla.
    </string>
    <string name="chicken_tanduri_ind">
1. 1 c. Greek yogurt
\n2. Juice of 1 lime
\n3. 1 clove garlic, minced
\n4. 1 tbsp. freshly grated ginger
\n5. 1 tsp. garam masala
\n6. 1/2 tsp. ground turmeric
\n7. Kosher salt
\8. Pinch of cayenne pepper
\n9. 2 lb. chicken legs</string>
    <string name="chicken_tanduri_pro">In a large bowl, whisk together yogurt, lime juice, garlic, ginger, garam masala, and turmeric and season with salt and cayenne. 
\n\nAdd chicken and toss until fully coated. Let marinate in the fridge at least 2 hours. 
\n\nWhen ready to bake, preheat oven to 400º and line a baking sheet with a wire rack. Bake chicken 20 minutes, then flip and bake 20 minutes more. Heat broiler and broil until skin is crispy, 2 minutes.</string>
    <string name="chicken_curry_ind">1 pound boneless skinless chicken breast chopped into bite sized pieces
1. 1 Tablespoon vegetable oil
\n2. 1 Tablespoon minced garlic
\n3. 1 small yellow or white onion chopped
\n4. 2 Tablespoons yellow curry powder
\n5. 1 Tablespoon Thai red curry paste
\n6. 15- ounce coconut milk canned, full fat
\n7. ½ cup water or chicken stock optional
\n8. 1 Tablespoon brown sugar
\n9. 1 teaspoon fish sauce
\n10. 2 Tablespoons lime juice
\n11. salt to taste
\n12. handful fresh cilantro roughly chopped
\n13. 4 cups cooked white rice</string>
    <string name="chicken_curry_pro">Heat the oil in a large pot over medium low heat. Add the onions and minced garlic and cook for a few minutes until the onions are fragrant and softened.
\n\nAdd the chicken and cook for 2-3 minutes, browning it a little. Add curry powder and paste; cook for 3-5 minutes.
\n\nAdd the coconut milk, and let simmer for 15-20 minutes or until the chicken is fully cooked.
\n\nAdd water or chicken stock depending on the consistency you want for the sauce, or let simmer longer to thicken if needed.
\n\nStir in the brown sugar, fish sauce, and lime juice. Taste and salt if needed
Top with fresh cilantro, serve over cooked rice.</string>
</resources>
